## Profile of Qualifications

More than 15 years of diverse Graphic Design experience featuring proficiency with InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat, and Microsoft Word, and Excel. Experience with both Macintosh and Windows operating systems. Articulate and organized, with positive attitude and consistent professionalism, providing excellent customer service. Work well autonomously or in team situations; accustomed to performing in fast-paced settings demanding strict deadline compliance and exceptional quality. Creative, goal focused, and motivated, with highly developed work ethic.

## **EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS**

• Touchmark, Beaverton, Oregon

2007 to 2012

Graphic Designer

Created marketing materials (ads, flyers, brochures, Word templates, floor plans, etc.) for 11 retirement communities and corporate office. Worked on multiple projects simultaneously with strict deadlines. Assisted Marketing Manager with trafficking of tasks.

• Prime Time Communications, Beaverton, Oregon

2006 to 2007

Graphic Designer

Responsible for all graphic design projects from initial stage to the printing process. Extensive customer interaction, troubleshooting client created files, output and develop film and maintain processor chemicals, organize and archive all graphics jobs.

• Kobalt Design Group/Signature Graphics, Portland, Oregon

2004 to 2006

Graphic Designer

Produced multi-page documents, brochures, flyers, direct mail pieces, and special grocery advertising items. Acquired and archived digital art, applying color correction and clipping path. Assisted other department staff as needed.

• Creative Process/Unified Western Grocers, Milwaukie, Oregon

1998 to 2003

Thriftway Art Director (1999-2003)

Designed, laid out, and typeset four-color weekly ad of up to 12 pages. Developed several ads simultaneously, attentive to weekly deadline. Prepared Internet and pdf files; interfaced with clients, vendors, ad agencies, and other decision makers. Created artwork for banners, buttons, and specialty projects. Used digital camera and scanner; wrote limited amounts of copy; styled and photographed food for Deli/Bakery Department.

Created special holiday and seasonal wine ads for publication in The Oregonian. Designed and produced Angus beef brochure.

Thriftway Production Artist (1998-1999)

Typeset, arranged layout for, and designed monthly coupon book. Assisted with production of weekly ad. Utilized scanner and digital camera; completed color correction.

## OTHER EXPERIENCE

- One year as volunteer for Cedar Mill Community Library.
- Six months as Sales Representative for First Light/7 Dees Nursery. Processed transactions and educated customers about plants, soils, and chemicals. Also created displays and completed wholesale orders.

## **EDUCATION**

Associate of Applied Science, Graphic Design, Portland Community College

1995